<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stop Brexit Party</title>
    <link>http://stopbrexit.party/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stop Brexit Party</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 12:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://stopbrexit.party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Change the default - stop a crash-out Brexit</title>
      <link>http://stopbrexit.party/posts/stop-crash-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stopbrexit.party/posts/stop-crash-out/</guid>
      <description>When Parliament returns, we need to change the default from crash-out no deal Brexit to Revoking Article 50 and remaining in the EU. There is no majority in the country or Parliament for a damaging crash-out Brexit, but there is a lot of disagreement on what we should do instead. Accordingly the first thing Parliament, or any new interim PM should do is pass a Bill to prevent an accidental Crash Out Brexit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign up for the Party</title>
      <link>http://stopbrexit.party/posts/party/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 10:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stopbrexit.party/posts/party/</guid>
      <description>You should already have your invitation in the post. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it or lost it, look it up here. Next, make an event for it - on Facebook, or by email - and invite your friends and neighbours. This is the one I made for my polling station - make one for your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sick of Brexit? Lets Party</title>
      <link>http://stopbrexit.party/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stopbrexit.party/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been 3 years. The Brexit fanclub have been in charge of government and at the end of it we have a bad proposal and a plan to have not plans and keep us in the Brexit loop forever. Over 6 million people signed a petition to revoke Article 50 and stop Brexit dead. Now we have an EU Election to vote in, and every vote in that is a vote for the EU.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>